Matthew Childs

PROFILE

......

Technologist with 4 years experience in the consulting sector. Values a user centered approach and is comfortable working in both advisory & delivery roles. Has experience working from strategy, to prototype development, delivery and support. Looking to secure a consulting position at an international organisation. Willing to relocate.

EMPLOYMENT

Atos Consulting

2011 - 2013

Assistant Consultant, London (UK)

CIO Advisory Digital Strategy Practice. Large business transformation projects carrying out Business Analysis, Test Management, User Experience activities & Software Development. Working across many business verticals (Education, Media, Energy, Transport, Insurance, Government) with clients such as BP, Pearson, BBC, East Coast Rail & Liverpool Victoria.

EMC Consulting

20I0 **-** 20II

Associate Practice Consultant, London (UK)

Software testing on financial and retail projects for clients such as ASOS & Close Brothers. Tasks included: Creation & execution of test plans using automation where possible, Managing user acceptance testing. All work was carried out in cross functional agile (scrum) teams.

EMC Consulting (Conchango)

2008 – 2009

Industrial Placement Student, London (UK)

Front-end development, Software testing & Business Analysis across a number of business verticals (retail, energy, finance) with clients such as Anglo American & Barclaycard.

EDUCATION

......

BSc (Hons) Computing (2:1)

Bournemouth University (UK)

2006 - 2010

National Diploma for IT Practitioner (Distinction)

Farnborough College of Technology (UK) 2004 - 2006

Chinese Language Program (B+)

National Taichung University of Education (Taiwan) 2013 - 2014

REFERENCES

Available on request.

SKILLS

Language

Mandarin (Intermediate)

English (Native)

.....

<u>Development</u>

HTML5 (Expert)
CSS3 (Expert)

JavaScript (Intermediate)
PHP (Intermediate)

C# .NET (Basic)

Consulting

Certified Scrum Master

Presentation

Business Analysis

.....

Hypothesis driven approach

SOFTWARE

Software Development

Microsoft Visual Studio

Sublime Text

Design

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Axure Pro

Balsamiq

<u>General</u>

Microsoft Office Suite

Google App's

.....

CONTACT



hello@mattc.co



+886975084442



Taichung, Taiwan